Lucas William Bateson



Contact

Address:

Bekkelagsveien 20B Oslo, Norway 1177 Oslo

Phone:

+47 934 007 38

Email:

lucas.bateson@gmail.com

Languages

English – Native Norwegian – Native German – Beginner (Studied for 3 years at school)

Summary

I am a 16-year-old student studying Information technology and Media production at Fyrstikkallen Vgs in Oslo, Norway. I am a dual British/Norwegian National, although I am born and raised in Oslo.

Skills

- Backend development using Python Flask.
- Vue.js frontend.

Html, CSS and JavaScript for website creation.

Experience

Programming teacher Aug 2020 – Jun 2021

Oslo commune, Oslo

- Responsible for helping grade 4 students learn block programming.

Scout Leader Aug 2018 - present

Oslo

- Responsible for a patrol of 10 scouts ensuring well-being and safety on trips.
- Responsible for giving guidance to patrol leaders on how to lead their patrols.
- Completed multiple courses with a focus on leadership skills

Media production Sept 2022 – present

Jordal AMFI, Oslo

- Producing the live video replays for a media cube during multiple live hockey matches using a 3Play video capture/replay solution.
- Working as a camera operator with a professional production team.

Education

Fyrstikkallen Vgs

Aug 2022 – Present

- Information technology and media production studies

Grades

Grades range from 1-6 with 1-2 being low competence, 3-4 being medium competence, and 5-6 being high competence:

- 6 Programming, Vocational Studies
- 5 Maths, English, Science, P.E, Technological understanding, Storytelling

Hobbies

Scouts, Skiing, Online gaming, Microelectronics and Programming